Till date in my life I have not been able to keep the fast on Monday of Sawan.  I keep
sucking all day long.
That is why God neither gave any boon nor any boon.   If I have
given it then my tongue keeps moving like scissors, making the sound of 'khach khach khach'.  This is what
my mother says.
And today Mother woke me up at 5:00 in the morning.  She is
saying that everyone is going to the temple.
You also go away.  Good sense will
come.  Okay mom, by the time I regained consciousness from 5:00, I did
n't even realize when it became 8:00.
Now let me get ready quickly before my mother wraps me in a wrap.
This borrowed suit from my mother and these Kashmiri
bangles which I got on my birthday.  So after
wearing the dress, I do some light makeup
and before doing my hair, I do a
light massage with Alps Goodness Rosemary Water.
Because you might have noticed that a
lot of hair falls during monsoon.  So I
spray it directly on the scalp and
massage it with my finger tips.  Due to which
hair fall reduces up to three times.  It
improves blood circulation in the scalp.
Also boosts hair growth in 12 weeks.  It is
light weight and non
greasy.  Therefore, there is no need to wash hair after applying it.
India's first
and only clinically proven rosemary water.  That's why
I have tagged the perp to get it.
So this is the final look but
still something seems missing so I
thought why not attach small cute flowers to this braid.
After that
I came to pluck the Kaner flowers and see
what fragrance is coming from them.  Wow!  And yes, I forgot to wish
you all a very happy Sawan.
Radhe-Radhe.